let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 21,
    "question": "Which of these is not a measure of absolute population density?",
    "answer": "pelt count",
    "options": [
      "total count",
      "pelt count",
      "capture-recapture method",
      "removal method"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 22,
    "question": "The juvenile mortality rate is the annual number of deaths of juveniles per",
    "answer": "1000 live births",
    "options": [
      "100 births",
      "1000 births",
      "100 live births",
      "1000 live births"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 23,
    "question": "_____ is how close the measured values are to the correct values",
    "answer": "accuracy",
    "options": [
      "accuracy",
      "precision",
      "bias",
      "variance"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 24,
    "question": "____ employs a simple rule of selecting every kth unit starting with a number chosen at random from 1 to k as the random start",
    "answer": "systematic sampling",
    "options": [
      "simple random sampling",
      "systematic sampling",
      "stratified sampling",
      "multistage sampling"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 25,
    "question": "Cover board surveys are typically used for sampling",
    "answer": "herpetofauna",
    "options": [
      "herpetofauna",
      "fishes",
      "large mammals",
      "carnivores"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 26,
    "question": "The minimum replacement level fertility for a population to grow should be greater than",
    "answer": "2",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 27,
    "question": "The logistic growth curve, when plotted, appears",
    "answer": "S shaped",
    "options": [
      "I shaped",
      "J shaped",
      "S shaped",
      "O shaped"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 28,
    "question": "Pan traps are used for sampling",
    "answer": "pollinator insects",
    "options": [
      "bees",
      "butterflies",
      "non-pollinator insects",
      "pollinator insects"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 29,
    "question": "A sampling procedure such that each possible combination of sampling units out of the population has the same chance of being selected is referred to as",
    "answer": "simple random sampling",
    "options": [
      "simple random sampling",
      "systematic sampling",
      "stratified sampling",
      "multistage sampling"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 30,
    "question": "Which of these is true?",
    "answer": "a or b",
    "options": [
      "physiological longevity > ecological longevity",
      "physiological longevity = ecological longevity",
      "physiological longevity < ecological longevity",
      "a or b"
    ]
}]